[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The actress, who plays Rudy on The Cosby Show, plays Leroys little sister in The Last Dragon.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What famous singer and actress starred in the 1972 comedy movie Whats Up, Doc??", "correct_answer": "Barbra Streisand", "incorrect_answers": ["Cher", "Gloria Estefan", "Liza Minnelli"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If I weighed 100 pounds(45.5 Kilograms) on Earth, about how much would I weigh on Mars?", "correct_answer": "37.7 Pounds(17.1 Kilograms)", "incorrect_answers": ["90.7 Pounds(41.2 Kilograms)", "48.6 Pounds(22.1 Kilograms)", "88.9 Pounds(40.4 Kilograms)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Was the year 1912 a leap year?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For what county did Chinatown character Claude Mulvihill serve as sheriff?", "correct_answer": "Ventura", "incorrect_answers": ["Orange", "Marin", "Los Angeles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How old was Bobby Fischer when he won the US chess championship on January 8th 1958?", "correct_answer": "14", "incorrect_answers": ["12", "22", "19"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is a special Eskimo dish. They gut this animal and stuff it with dead seagulls. Its left underground to mature for a while and then they would have a dinner feasts.", "correct_answer": "Gull-stuffed walrus", "incorrect_answers": ["Retsina", "Gull-stuffed dog", "Borscht"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the famous Welsh poet who wrote the poem The Boys of Summer.", "correct_answer": "Dylan Thomas", "incorrect_answers": ["James Joyce", "Theodore Roethke", "e.e. cummings"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tigers are native to what continent?", "correct_answer": "Asia", "incorrect_answers": ["Australia", "Africa", "America"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did NASAs first satellite, Explorer I, find?", "correct_answer": "The Van Allen radiation belt", "incorrect_answers": ["That Mars natural satellites were actually captured asteroids", "The remains of Sputnik I", "Jupiters moon Callisto"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When something is especially cleaned one is said to have applied polish and ..........  to it.", "correct_answer": "Spit", "incorrect_answers": ["Ajax", "Elbow grease", "Cleanser"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Charles Johnson was a pioneering United States aviator famous for piloting the first solo non-stop flight across the Atlantic Ocean in 1927.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]